hey everyone thanks for listening to The
Grow Your Life podcast I'm excited that
you're here I'm excited for this episode
I've been studying something all week by
the way I have a little bit of a head
cold so apologize for the sound being
off but the content is going to be fire
today and so if you can look past the
the sound of my voice you're going to
find that the that what I'm going to be
talking about is going to be impactful
on our coaching call that we had with my
group on Thursday we talked about a
concept that I've been studying a little
bit and I want to unpack it on this call
with you to help you get a lot of impact
one of the biggest things I've noticed
that prevents us from getting our offers
out there from launching and and let me
just instead of talking about what
prevents us but what has prevented me
what have I struggled with what have I
been dealing with is I
have felt that I have to be very careful
with how I say things what I say my tone
of voice how I come across trying to
present this perfect version of myself
all the time to people and I'll tell you
this
um it's not authentic when I do that I
don't show up with the the best content
my brain is too focused on sounding good
that I don't actually like say good
stuff because I'm so focused on how I
sound and look and act and all that
stuff that the words actually coming out
of my mouth are are are a lower tier of
quality and I know that people follow me
for the stuff they actually say they
actually want to hear it that it's it's
really good stuff when I get out of my
head get out of my own way and stop
worrying about do I look right sound
right am I acting right so I want to
live by example on this I want to share
with you what I what I learned and what
I studied is it's this idea of the
perfectionistic communicator part so
it's so it goes beyond just
perfectionism okay because that can that
can apply in many different ways but now
we're getting specific and by the way
this is a great technique that you can
use um in your own life is getting
specific around those areas like if I
just say you're a perfectionist it's
like well yeah like that that can be a
good thing in some ways um but at the at
the same time like perfectionistic
Communicator around the area of your
communication okay um I find for me that
doesn't
work I've tried it it just I don't show
up very well and my clients who follow
me they have found that the reasons why
they don't launch their offers they
don't get them out there is they're
worried about way too often how they
sound how their tonality is if their
words are perfect the words they put in
an email if the words they put on their
sales copy and by the way these are all
things that are within our control to be
able to produce better results so this
is where it's like a sort of a
double-edged sword because if you can
improve the words you say your tonality
all of that in a much better
way it'll have a better result the
problem is if you focus on that and your
focus is having the perfect tonality the
perfect
words the the part of your brain that
actually is going to like come up with
the good stuff to say the good words is
going to be spending way too much energy
on making sure we
are sounding right saying it in the
right way and and all of that instead of
just flowing just being ourselves and I
find that when I can just be myself and
I can just show up in that way and and I
get out of my head of am I saying this
right oh gosh did I say those words
right am I using the right tone am I
connecting right two things crazily
happen I connect way better my tongue
own and all of that is
better yes there's a few areas where I
mess up on yes there's a few areas where
I'm like not the best I can scrutinize
that and I become my own worst critic we
become our own worst critic in these
areas and so a giving ourselves Grace
over our
communication
styles to just do our
best and if you can do that the rest is
going to work itself out I promise you
that
if you can get into a place where you
believe in yourself that you think that
you are the most amazing person out
there that everybody should listen to
that's going to impact people that that
you're the bees knees that you're
awesome that you're
just the is you know you're incredible
at what you do and you show up with that
self-belief it's not arrogance At All by
the way um it sounds like arrogance when
I'm explaining it that way but it's
actually it it it uh it comes across
actually in a very authentic humble way
like like like a natural humility that
people like and and resonate with you're
not trying to get people to like you
type of a thing whenever we're trying to
get somebody to like us
um a connection goes out the window
because we're in a
defensiveness and and what we're trying
to defend is proving that we're good
enough to do the things that we already
have evidence that we're good enough to
do and that's what I was experiencing my
life I have
evidence like crazy 21 almost 22 years
in my
industry of success doing what I've been
doing and yet feeling like okay I I'm
not going to appear good enough to
people for them to want to work with me
unless I have the perfect tonality
communication and all that okay
something's got to give here and and and
that's where a lack of connection
started to come in with people and I was
finding myself avoiding launching offers
avoiding sending emails avoiding making
social media content avoiding making
YouTube videos avoiding recording even
podcast episodes like this because I
felt like I had
to make sure everything I said was
perfect and really craft this
perfect narrative and I'll tell you
again there's some people they love that
knock themselves out I think they they
can go do that but if they're not
getting the results they want and this
is the key whenever I do
that I don't get the results that I want
in my business and a lot of my clients
don't either I know like I can think of
a handful of people off the top of my
head who they are like that and they
actually do get really good results keep
doing it if that's you like you know
that's awesome but nine times out of
10 there's a different result you want
to be getting than you are getting and
so if we can learn to kind of release
some of that perfectionistic
Communicator
part and like give ourselves Grace to
it's okay if you stutter or you say the
wrong thing and then you correct it real
quick uh or like you got the wrong
slightly body language or you use the
wrong words on a sales letter or in an
email or or like like it's okay to not
have to be perfect it's it's okay you're
not going to lose trust in people and
you might argue well that's not true I
will lose trust in certain people I
could lose potential business people
only do business with those that are
professionals can I tell you this those
people that you would lose would never
do business with you in the first
place
ever but you will lose people that you
could actually do business with by
needing to make everything perfect and
this is what I found was happening for
me as I was pushing away the good people
the people that I needed to work with
the people that I was meant to work
with when I do this and when I when I
just am myself I'm not concerned about
saying it all perfect and doing all the
perfect
stuff I connect a lot better with people
you might be noticing like even this
podcast episode it's probably one of the
better ones you've listened to for me
I'm sure you like the the how I'm
flowing like it feels like we're talking
we're connecting we're sitting acoss a
kitchen table together that's what I'm
talking about I'm not caught up in my
head I am not even thinking about am I
saying thisf I have like I said I have a
stuffy nose like I said at the beginning
of this I I apologize for that I told
you this is going to be some of the best
content that you've heard me
say whereas about a couple weeks ago
maybe I wouldn't I would have felt so
upset that I had a stuffy nose and not
even record something because of that so
if we can get out of that
modality and into let me just be myself
show
up however it lands lands hope for the
best stay consistent with actually doing
the work rather than needing to do the
work
perfect you will get far greater
results every single time especially
when it comes to how you communicate
your emails your sales copy your social
media content your video video content
all that any sort of form of external
outward Communications that you're doing
with people cuz that's where I was
really struggling with it and that's
what I find some of my clients do as
well and if we can start
to make peace with the fact that like
it's so like it's okay to just be
ourselves and and have confidence and
belief in ourselves that's not based on
performance that oh I feel confident
because I'm doing
perfect no it's cuz I feel confident cuz
I'm amazing and I know that people need
to listen to me and they're going to get
their socks knocked off by listening to
me and that everything in their life is
going to be better after they meet me
and I have that mentality and I go into
it with that mentality and what comes
out is the best stuff all right so I
hope this has helped you uh pass it on
to somebody who might need to hear this
this podcast is is worth
sharing make sure you follow and listen
if if you're a coach trainer mentor and
you want to have me become a part of
your success strategy uh come alongside
you Mentor you coach you become your
support your accountability be able to
point out are your ads right is your
sales copyright how's your presentations
how your landing pages all of the
aspects of your business and you want me
to work with you to make all that stuff
actually work incredibly um we' love to
have you be a part of our client growth
CER program so I work with people on
that every single week and I'd love to
help you with that as well all right
we'll talk soon go
[Applause]
[Music]